- Attention, Edgewood students.
- 注意了，Edgewood的学生们。
The rosters for all clubs and sports teams
所有俱乐部和运动队的名单
are now being posted.
现在正在公布。
Go, Buffaloes.
加油，野牛队。
- I'm so nervous.
- 我好紧张。
What if I didn't make the team?
如果我没入选怎么办？
It'll be terrible.
那太糟糕了。
I'll be humiliated.
我会感到羞辱。
But what if I did?
但如果我入选了呢？
Imagine.
想象一下。
I'll be the first fifth grader
我将成为第一个五年级学生
to ever make the sixth grade team.
加入六年级队伍。
I'll be a legend.
我将成为一个传奇。
But what if I didn't?
但如果我没成功呢？
It'll be like a horrible kick in the shins.
那感觉就像被狠狠踢了一脚小腿。
- Ow, can we switch now?
- 哎哟，我们现在能换吗？
- Pfft, no way.
- 哼，不可能。
- I can't look.
- 我都不敢看。
- Don't worry. I got your back.
- 别担心，我支持你。
- Don't leave me.
- 别离开我。
- Say konnichiwa
向日本语俱乐部的新会长问好
to the new president of the Japanese Language Club.
这在我的大学申请上会看起来很棒
This is gonna look subarashii on my college applications.
那怎么就算一个俱乐部了，他们却不让我创办
- How is that a club, but they wouldn't let me start
亲迪基一美元俱乐部？
the Kiss Dicky For $1 Club?
道恩！道恩，你入选了！
- Dawn! Dawn, you made the team!
是的！
- Yes! - Ow.
哎哟。
- ♪ I made the soccer team ♪
♪ 我加入了足球队 ♪
♪ I made the soccer team ♪
♪ 我加入了 足球队 ♪
[laughs] What's up, teammates?
[笑] 大家好，队友们？
Feels so good to say that.
这么说感觉真好。
Teammates. Teamies.
队友们。团队伙伴们。
- Look, Dawn, you may have made the team,
- 看，Dawn，你可能加入了球队，
but you haven't made "the team."
但你还没有成为“那个团队”的一员。
Come on, team.
来吧，团队。
- So I made the team but I haven't made "the team?"
- 所以我加入了球队但我还没有成为“那个团队”的一员？
What does that mean?
这是什么意思？
[panicky] What does that mean?
[慌张] 这是什么意思？
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- [有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[girls laughing]
[女孩们笑声]
- What should I do?
- 我该怎么办？
I mean, I don't know what to do,
我是说，我不知道该做什么，
but what do you think I should do?
但你觉得我应该怎么做？
- Well, first you stab the food with your fork,
- 嗯，首先用叉子戳食物，
then lift the fork to your mouth and let the teeth take over.
然后把叉子举到嘴边，让牙齿接管。
- I know how to eat. It's just--
- 我知道怎么吃。只是——
I don't know what they meant about being on the team
我不知道他们说的在团队里和不在“团队”里是什么意思。
and not being on "the team."
- 看，那里有个空位。
- Look, there's an empty seat.
Just go over, sit down, and start talking.
就走过去，坐下，开始聊天。
You just learned how to eat.
你刚刚学会了怎么吃。
That's a conversation starter.
这是个开启对话的好方法。
- You're right.
你说得对。
I'm going in.
我要行动了。
Hey, soccer sisters.
嘿，足球姐妹们。
I'm psyched I made the team,
我很兴奋能加入球队，
but I got to ask,
但我得问一下，
how do I make "the team"?
我怎样才能成为“那个团队”的一员？
- Look, Dawn,
看，Dawn，
you're a newbie and team tradition is,
你是新人，而团队的传统是，
newbies have to pass the initiation
新人必须通过入会仪式
before they earn a place at our table.
才能在我们的桌子上赢得一席之地。
- Well, how do I do that?
- 那么，我该怎么做呢？
- Do something table-worthy.
- 做些值得上桌的事情。
We know you're a good soccer player,
我们知道你是个优秀的足球运动员，
but show us what other skills you have.
但展示一下你还有哪些其他技能。
Wow us.
让我们惊叹。
- Hmm.
- 嗯。
I speak some Japanese.
我会说一些日语。
Konnichi-what!
你好什么！
- Do you guys remember when Dawn was all, "konnichi-what!"
- 你们还记得Dawn当时说的，'你好什么！'吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- How come you guys didn't laugh when I did it?
- 为什么我做的时候你们不笑？
- It's much funnier with gloves on.
- 戴着手套做更有趣。
Everything is funnier with gloves on.
戴着手套做任何事都更有趣。
- Well, what about Kyle the mime?
- 那Kyle这个哑剧演员呢？
He's not funny.
他不好笑。
No offense, Kyle.
无意冒犯，Kyle。
- What are you studying for?
- 你在准备什么？
- Social Studies test.
社会学考试。
- Aren't we in the same Social Studies class?
我们不是在同一个社会学班吗？
- Yes, we are.
是的，我们在。
- Does that mean I have a Social Studies test?
那是不是意味着我也有社会学考试？
- Yes, you do.
是的，你有。
- Oh, well, then I better prepare...
哦，那我最好准备一下...
to get out of the test.
逃过这场考试。
I need just the right excuse.
我需要一个合适的借口。
Fake vomit?
假呕吐？
Nah, I use that to get out of Math.
不，我用那个逃数学课。
Ooh, bloody nose.
哦，流鼻血了。
- That's my shirt.
那是我的衬衫。
- I wasn't gonna ruin one of mine.
我可不想毁了我自己的。
That's the puddin'.
这就是布丁。
- Is that an X-ray?
那是一张X光片吗？
- Here comes Windpipe Williams.
风管威廉斯来了。
It's showtime.
表演时间到了。
- Please don't make him turn his head.
请别让他转头。
That weird voice thing freaks me out.
他那奇怪的嗓音让我害怕。
- Challenge accepted.
挑战接受。
- Hey, Harpers.
- 嘿，哈珀斯。
- Hi, Mr. Williams.
- 你好，威廉姆斯先生。
- Are you ready for the Social Studies test?
- 你们准备好社会学考试了吗？
- Pardon me?
- 你说什么？
- [constricted] I think you heard me.
- [声音受限] 我想你听到了。
- Right, about that test.
- 对了，关于那个考试。
There was a car accident.
发生了一起车祸。
- Is that a...
- 那是一个...
[constricted] Toy car in your sternum?
[声音受限] 你胸骨里的玩具车？
- Apparently I swallowed it during dinner.
- 显然我晚餐时吞下了它。
Guess I ate too fast, too furious.
我想是我吃得又快又猛。
- Hmm.
嗯。
[constricted] Ricky, is your brother...
[声音受限]瑞奇，你哥哥...
[normal voice] Telling the truth?
[正常声音]说的是真话吗？
- I, uh...
我，呃...
- Go ahead, Ricky.
说吧，瑞奇。
Tell him the truth.
告诉他真相。
- [voice modulating] A simple yes or no will suffice.
[声音调节]简单的‘是’或‘不是’就可以了。
- He's lying.
他在撒谎。
- Thank you for your honesty, Ricky.
谢谢你的真实回答，瑞奇。
I will see you both...
[constricted] in class.
[normal voice] Hey, Gail. [constricted] Wait up.
- Thanks a lot.
You're supposed to have my back.
You broke The Quad Code.
- You told me to tell the truth. - Not the real truth, the truth I wanted you to tell.
[sighs]
- Not funny, Kyle.
Dicky. - I'm not talking to you.
- But, Dicky-- - Everything okay, gentlemen?
- 但是，迪基-- - 一切都好吗，先生们？
- Yeah, just excited about the test.
- 是的，只是对考试感到兴奋。
High five.
击掌。
Whoops. Don't worry.
哎呀。别担心。
No arm, no foul. I'll just run to the nurse.
没有手臂，不算犯规。我跑去找护士。
- Oh, sure, sure. Let me get you a hall pass. There you go.
- 哦，当然，当然。让我给你一张通行证。给你。
Really?
真的吗？
- Now I got to go see the nurse about this weird extra hand.
- 现在我得去看看这只奇怪的多出来的手。
- Sit down, Dicky.
- 坐下，迪基。
- Dicky, listen.
- 迪基，听着。
- I'm not talking to you.
- 我不跟你说话。
- Mr. Williams, report to the parking lot.
- 威廉姆斯先生，请到停车场报到。
Your car is being towed.
你的车正在被拖走。
Go Buffaloes.
加油，野牛队。
- What?
- 什么？
[constricted] Why is my car being towed?
[声音紧绷] 为什么我的车要被拖走？
[normal voice] Today's test is...
[正常声音] 今天的考试是...
[voice cracking] postponed.
[声音颤抖] 推迟了。
- No test?
- 没有考试？
Yes! Yes!
是的！是的！
I can't wait to go home and celebrate.
- Shouldn't you go home and study?
- For what?
- Hey, do you think it's silly I got her one cake for good news
and one cake for bad news?
- I think it's silly that you made
the bad news cake chocolate.
I mean, I really want her to make the team,
but I really love chocolate cake.
I'm really being pulled in two directions here, Anne.
- Dawn, I know you didn't make "the team"...
- 道恩，我知道你没有被“选中”……
but at least you made the team.
- 但至少你加入了团队。
- Oh, sweetie! That's incredible.
- 哦，亲爱的！这太棒了。
I'm so proud of you.
- 我真为你感到骄傲。
We knew you'd make it.
- 我们一直知道你会成功的。
See?
- 看吧？
- The receipts and security tags are just for decoration.
- 收据和安全标签只是装饰用的。
- Thanks, guys.
- 谢谢大家。
- Let's go clean you a piece of cake.
- 我们去给你切块蛋糕吧。
- Yeah, have at it.
- 好的，尽情享用吧。
Enjoy.
请享用。
Good stuff.
好东西。
- So, pretty cool what happened in social studies today, huh?
- 今天社会学课上发生的事挺酷的，对吧？
- Yeah, good stuff happens to me all the time.
- 是啊，好事总是发生在我身上。
I'm pretty sure there's a word for that in Japanese.
我敢肯定日语里有个词来形容这个。
- It was me.
- 是我。
- Let me try that.
- 让我试试。
It-was-me.
是-我。
- No, it was me.
- 不，是我。
- It-was-me.
- 是-我。
- No, I called the tow truck company.
不，是我叫的拖车公司。
- I don't speak Japanese, man.
我不懂日语，伙计。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
- I got the test postponed!
我把考试延期了！
- So my "it-was-me" was because of you?
所以我的“是我”是因为你？
- Yes. Yes, it was.
是的。没错，是因为你。
- You covered for me?
你替我掩护了？
- It's The Quad Code.
这是四人规则。
Quads before quizzes.
四人优先于测验。
- Whoa, thanks, bro.
哇，谢谢，兄弟。
You got a guy's car towed for me.
你让人帮我拖走了那辆车。
You're a total rebel.
你真是个叛逆者。
- Well, say hello...
- 那么，跟他说声你好...
to Rebel Ricky.
到叛逆瑞奇。
- Can you imagine how much trouble you'd be in
- 你能想象如果威廉姆斯先生发现了，你会有多大的麻烦吗？
if Mr. Williams ever found out?
- 麻烦？什么意思？
- Trouble? What do you mean?
- 首先，你会被罚一个月的留校察看...
- Well, first you'd get, like, a month of detention...
留校察看？
- Detention?
- 甚至可能被学校开除。
- Maybe even kicked out of school.
开除出学校？
- K-kicked out of school?
- 被开除？
But if I get kicked out, it'll ruin my permanent record,
但如果我被开除，我的永久记录就毁了，
which means I definitely won't get into a good college,
这意味着我肯定进不了好大学，
and instead of being the first lawyer-president-astronaut,
而不是成为第一个律师-总统-宇航员，
I'm gonna be broke and alone, sleeping on your couch,
我会破产又孤独，睡在你的沙发上，
eating your pizza scraps for the rest of my life!
吃你剩下的披萨度过后半生！
- Dude, don't worry.
- 伙计，别担心。
That's never gonna happen.
那绝不会发生的。
I'd give you a month. Then you're out.
我会给你一个月时间。然后你就出局了。
- Excuse me, do you know what time it is?
- 打扰一下，你知道现在几点了吗？
'Cause I do.
因为我确实知道。
It's wow-o'clock, and Dawn's buying!
现在是哇哦时刻，Dawn请客！
- Kyle, I'm working here.
Kyle，我正在工作呢。
- Wow.
哇。
- I got a wow?
我得到了一个哇？
- Wrong kind of wow.
错了，不是那种哇。
Mm.
嗯。
- Nothing is working.
什么都没用。
Why won't my wow come out?
为什么我的哇出不来？
Maybe I'm just wow-stipated.
也许我只是哇堵塞了。
Or maybe I've lost my wow.
或者也许我已经失去了我的wow。
You're right.
你说得对。
I don't deserve to be on the team
我不配在这个团队里
or "the team."
或者说是“那个团队”。
Thanks for listening, Mary.
谢谢你听我说，Mary。
- Whoa, this is my jam.
哇，这是我喜欢的歌。
- Hey, team.
嘿，团队。
Nicky!
Nicky！
I'm so sorry. I'll get napkins.
非常抱歉。我去拿纸巾。
[girls giggling]
[女孩们咯咯笑]
- That was hilarious, Dawn.
那真是太搞笑了，Dawn。
- It was?
是吗？
- Total wow.
绝对的精彩。
- It was.
确实。
- The way you made it look like an accident?
你让它看起来像是个意外？
[all laugh]
大家都笑了
- Yep, totally did that on purpose.
对，完全是故意的。
But you knew that, 'cause the proof
但你早就知道了，因为事实胜于雄辩。
was in the pudding.
笑了
- [laughs]
Congratulations, Dawn.
恭喜你，Dawn。
Look like someone's ready for...
看起来有人已经准备好...
this.
这个了。
- Don't worry, everybody.
别担心，大家。
My sister's getting me napkins as we speak.
我妹妹正在给我们拿餐巾纸。
She's totally got my back.
她绝对支持我。
[kids murmuring]
孩子们低声议论。
- Oh, guess she doesn't.
哦，看来她没有。
[girls laughing]
女孩们笑了起来。
- You know, Dawn, I'm going to go out on a limb
你知道吗，Dawn，我要大胆地说
and say that pudding is the new gloves.
我要大胆地说，布丁就是新的手套。
- I got lots of ways to wow you.
我有很多方法让你惊叹。
But if you liked it,
但如果你喜欢它，
I'm not "pudding" up a fight.
我不会为布丁而战。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- We'll see you at your dad's store.
我们会在你爸爸的店里见。
- See you there.
那里见。
[groans]
[呻吟]
Have you guys seen Nicky?
你们看到尼基了吗？
I got to talk to him. - You can't.
我得和他谈谈。 - 你不能。
Mom picked him up after you "dessert-ed" him.
妈妈在你'甜点逃亡'后把他接走了。
- Was he mad at me? - He didn't say.
- 他生我的气吗？ - 他没说。
- He couldn't.
- 他没法说。
His face was crusted shut with pudding.
他的脸被布丁粘得说不出话来。
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
- Well, I'm off to Japanese Language Club.
- 好了，我要去日语俱乐部了。
Sayonara.
再见。
- Hey, Harpers.
- 嘿，哈珀斯。
I was talking with the tow truck company, and apparently,
我刚和拖车公司聊过，显然，
a little boy called using a fake Japanese accent.
有个小男孩用假日本口音打电话。
And I know exactly who it was.
而且我知道是谁干的。
- You do?
- 你知道？
- Of course I do, Ricky.
- 当然知道，Ricky。
[constricted] It was Dicky.
[压抑的声音] 是Dicky。
Both: What? - Don't act innocent.
双方: 什么？ - 别装无辜。
You faked the X-ray, you faked...
你伪造了X光片，你伪造了...
[constricted] your hand falling off,
[压抑的声音] 你的手掉下来，
[normal voice] And you faked being
[正常声音] 还有你伪造了
concerned Japanese citizen...
关心日本公民的身份...
[constricted] Ricky-san.
[压抑的声音] Ricky-san。
- Mr. Williams, I promise, it wasn't me.
- 威廉姆斯先生，我发誓，不是我。
Ask Ricky. He'll tell you.
- 问里奇。他会告诉你的。
- [constricted] Ricky?
- 里奇？
- Go ahead, Ricky.
- 说吧，里奇。
You like telling the truth, remember?
你喜欢说实话，记得吗？
Imagine how much trouble you'd be in?
想象一下你会惹上多大的麻烦？
Month of detention,
一个月的拘留，
kicked out of school. Kicked out of school!
被学校开除。被学校开除！
It was me!
是我！
- Dicky did it! - What?
- 迪基干的！ - 什么？
- I knew it. Detention.
- 我就知道。留校察看。
[constricted] Come with me.
[紧张] 跟我来。
- What happened to quads before quizzes?
- 测验前的四轮车是怎么回事？
- I don't want to hear it, Kyle.
- 我不想听，凯尔。
- Nicky, there you are.
- 尼基，你在这儿。
Here are those napkins just like I promised.
这些餐巾纸就像我承诺的那样。
- Little late.
- 有点晚了。
I spent two hours scraping pudding off my body.
我花了两个小时从身上刮掉布丁。
My face came off in one piece.
我的脸整张脱落了。
- Nicky, it was an accident.
- 尼基，那是意外。
I swear I would never do something like that to you on purpose.
我发誓我绝不会故意对你做那样的事。
- I guess you're right.
- 我想你是对的。
I know you wouldn't.
我知道你不会。
- I'm really sorry.
- 我真的很抱歉。
Are you mad at me?
你生我的气吗？
- How could I be mad?
- 我怎么会生气呢？
You wowed the soccer girls,
你让那些足球女孩刮目相看，
mom bought me this sweet new track suit,
妈妈给我买了这件超酷的新运动服，
and my face is pudding soft.
我的脸现在像布丁一样柔软。
- So we're cool?
- 所以我们没事了？
- We're cool.
Now go make me proud.
- How it goes, Buffaloes?
- You know, Dawn, if you're gonna officially be one of us,
you'll be needing one of these.
- Wow. - You earned it.
That pudding bit was hilar.
- So hilar.
Wish I could see it again.
- Yep, too bad no one video-ed it
so you could watch it over and over.
这样你就可以一遍又一遍地看。
- That's a great idea.
那是个好主意。
You should dump pudding on your brother again,
你应该再往你弟弟头上倒一次布丁，
but this time, we'll get it with our phones.
但这次，我们用手机拍下来。
- You know, these things are never as funny the second time,
你知道，这些事情第二次做起来就没那么好笑了，
so...
所以...
So, about that headband?
那么，关于那个头带的事？
I got a head. You got a band.
我有头，你有带子。
Let's make this happen. - Not yet.
让我们实现它。
We have to get that on video.
还不行。
- But what if I don't want to dump pudding on Nicky again?
- 但如果我不想再往尼基身上倒布丁怎么办？
- Sorry, Dawn, but we told you.
- 对不起，Dawn，但我们告诉过你。
Newbies have to do whatever the team says.
新人必须做团队说的任何事。
- That's the way it's always been.
- 一直都是这样。
It's tradition.
这是传统。
- And now it's your turn.
- 现在轮到你了。
See you at lunch tomorrow.
明天午餐见。
- Great news.
- 好消息。
Mom said I can wear this bad boy
妈妈说我可以明天戴着这个家伙去学校，只要不弄脏它。
to school tomorrow as long as I don't get anything on it.
- 但我没有叫拖车。为什么你不相信我？
- But I didn't call a tow truck.
- 但我没有叫拖车。
Why don't you believe me?
你为什么不相信我？
- Because this year you have already set free
- 因为今年你已经
a tank full of turtles to get out of a Biology test.
放走了一池塘的乌龟来逃避生物考试。
- Faked an allergic reaction to pencils
- 假装对铅笔过敏
to get out of a Math test.
来逃避数学考试。
- And let's not forget about the time you got out of
- 而且别忘了那次你通过假装看到外面的狼
an English essay by pretending to see a wolf outside.
来逃避英语作文。
- You're literally the boy who cried wolf.
- 你简直就是那个喊狼来了的男孩。
- But I didn't do it this time.
- 但这次我真的没有这么做。
- Fine, Dicky.
If you didn't do it, then who did?
- I don't know who did it,
but I wish whoever did would come forward
and help a brother out.
- Well, you're grounded.
- For a month. - Ah, come on.
That's six whole weeks.
- It'll give you time to brush up on your Social Studies.
- Maybe take a glance at a calendar.
- Dude, how can you just sit there?
伙计，你怎么能就这样坐在那儿？
Tell them the truth.
告诉他们真相。
- I can't tell the truth.
我不能说实话。
My future's riding on this.
我的未来全靠这个了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I wish I could be a bad boy like you, but I'm not.
我希望我能像你一样做个坏孩子，但我不是。
- You're right.
你说得对。
You're not a bad boy.
你不是个坏孩子。
You're a bad guy.
你是个坏人。
- White suit coming through.
穿白西装的来了。
- Dawn?
- 黎明？
- Oh, hey!
- 哦，嘿！
Didn't see you there at the place you always are.
没看到你总是在那儿。
- What are you doing? Sit down.
- 你在做什么？坐下。
Look at this ginormous bowl of pudding.
看看这巨大的布丁碗。
We're ready.
我们准备好了。
- Yep, totally gonna do this.
- 是的，绝对要这么做。
All right.
好吧。
Here I go.
我要开始了。
Better walk slow to avoid spilling.
最好慢慢走，避免洒出来。
- Here you go.
给你。
- I can get my own spork, Ricky.
我可以自己拿勺叉，Ricky。
- Thought you weren't talking to me.
我以为你不跟我说话了。
- I'm not.
我没在说。
Starting now.
从现在开始。
- Could you grab me some napkins, please?
你能帮我拿些餐巾纸吗？
- Sure.
当然。
Starting now.
从现在开始。
- Nicky told me what you did, Ricky.
Nicky告诉我你做了什么，Ricky。
You should get the silent treatment.
你应该接受沉默对待。
You should also get the strawberry pretzel salad.
你应该也来一份草莓脆饼沙拉。
- Good news, dicky.
好消息，迪基。
I've got something fun planned for detention today.
今天留堂我安排了些有趣的活动。
You'll be scraping chewing gum off the bottom of desks.
你得把口香糖从桌底刮下来。
And the nose gum.
还有鼻涕糖。
Know what I mean? - Yes.
明白我的意思吗？ - 是的。
- That's boogers.
那是鼻屎。
- I said I know.
我说我知道了。
- Lots and lots and lots of nose gum.
很多很多的鼻涕糖。
In fact, there's almost no chewing gum at all.
实际上，几乎没有什么口香糖。
No, it's all nose gum.
不，全是鼻涕。
Which is boogers.
那就是鼻屎。
- I called the tow truck.
我叫了拖车。
[constricted] - What?
什么？
[normal voice] Ricky, you do not have to cover for your brother.
Ricky，你不必为你的哥哥掩饰。
- I'm not covering.
我没有掩饰。
It's the truth.
这是真的。
- Dawn?
Dawn？
You're still here.
你还在这儿。
- Okay, here I go.
好的，我来了。
Double time.
加快速度。
- There's no way Ricky did this. - Yes, he did.
- 这不可能是Ricky干的。 - 就是他干的。
- Why won't you just believe me?
- 你为什么不相信我？
- Because you're Ricky.
- 因为你是Ricky。
Everyone knows you don't have it in you.
大家都知道你没这个胆量。
- If I didn't have it in me, would I do this?
- 如果我没这个胆量，我会这么做吗？
Both: Ricky!
两人: Ricky！
- That's for trying to dump pudding on Nicky.
- 这是因为你试图把布丁倒在Nicky身上。
- You were going to dump pudding on me?
- 你打算把布丁倒在我身上？
Again? - On purpose.
又一次？ - 故意的。
- Wow, Ricky, thanks for having my back.
- 哇，Ricky，谢谢你支持我。
- What was that for?
- 那是为什么？
- For not having Dicky's back.
- 因为你没有支持Dicky。
- Thanks, Nicky.
- 谢谢，Nicky。
But Ricky just tried to make things right.
但Ricky刚刚试图弥补。
So according to The Quad Code.
所以根据Quad Code。
- That's it. All three of you...
- 就是这样。你们三个...
[voice modulating] detention for the entire month.
[声音调节]整个一个月的留校。
- That's 40 whole days!
- 那可是整整40天！
- And the next person who gets even a crumb of food
- 下一个哪怕在地上弄到一丁点食物的人
on the floor gets to join them.
地板上哪怕有一丁点食物，那个人也得加入他们。
- Sorry, Mr. Williams,
对不起，威廉姆斯先生，
I can't let my brothers go to detention alone.
我不能让我的兄弟们独自去禁闭。
It's The Quad Code.
这是四方守则。
- Not my face.
别打我的脸。
- Well, at least there's enough nose gum for the four of you.
至少有足够的鼻涕给你们四个人。
That's boogers.
那是鼻屎。
[constricted] See you in detention.
禁闭室见。
- [laughing] That was so hilar.
太搞笑了。
- [laughing] It was hyster.
真是笑死人了。
- But we were laughing so hard we forgot to record it.
但是我们笑得太厉害了，忘了录下来。
You need to do it again.
你需要再做一次。
- No.
不行。
- What?
什么？
- Look, I want to be on the soccer team,
你看，我想加入足球队，
but not if I can't be on this team.
但如果我不能加入这个队伍，那就算了。
And I'm not gonna be a part of your dumb old traditions.
我不想参与你们那些愚蠢的老传统。
The only way I should have to wow you is on the soccer field.
我唯一应该让你们惊叹的地方是在足球场上。
- But this is the way it's always been.
但这是我们一直以来的方式。
- Well, maybe it's time for a change.
嗯，也许现在是时候改变了。
This school hasn't won a championship in 27 years,
这所学校已经27年没有赢得冠军了，
but I'm hoping we can end that tradition too.
但我希望我们也能结束这一传统。
- Maybe we have been focusing on the wrong team.
- 也许我们一直关注错了队伍。
- Yeah, I didn't really like it when we were newbies.
- 是啊，当我们还是新手时，我并不喜欢那样。
- Then maybe it's time we start some new traditions.
- 那么，也许是时候开始一些新的传统了。
See you at practice tomorrow, teammate.
明天训练见，队友。
- Oh, I'll be there.
- 哦，我会去的。
Right after detention.
拘留结束后就去。
- You know, there is an upside to getting dumped on.
- 你知道，被抛弃也有好处。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
- [欢快旋律]
- ♪